<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TrendBiz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TrendBiz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 04:35:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 04:35:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/first/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cloud works! Our entire infrastructure is based on Amazon Web Services (AWS). Whether you are a large enterprise, an SME or a startup;
whether you are into banking or education, R&amp;amp;D or service, TrendBiz has the cloud solution befitting your needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cater to the specific business requirements of each organization. This ensures that all your IT needs are met.
Cloud services facilitate use of the latest, most advanced IT resources without having to buy them. Pay-As-You-Go services can be integrated into your service
plan to help you access better resources at a competent price. Grow faster with better IT resources at your disposal without having to actually own them.
Get higher Computing Power with efficient information transfer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Access your enterprise data and manage it from anywhere around the globe. Pay only for what you use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scale up or scale down your computing capacity within minutes, depending on your needs. Gain quick accessto increased storage and resources.
Choose your specification as per your business. Multiple layers of security to ensure safety and integrity of your data, application and IP.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Consulting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/last/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 04:36:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/last/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;audit:a7f4ea7861853ea0de97008ab620749e&#34;&gt;Audit&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We audit your company in professional manner by Licensed Auditors. We have a staff for audit matters with people of different profiles such as:
Engineer, Architect, Manager, IT Administrator, IT Programmer, Accountant, Audit Assistant etc.
Success of your company in achieving the aspirations is our goal. However analyzing the activities and actions of an Entity (Firm, Entrepreneurship) for assuring
they are done or are functioning in accordance with objectives, business plan, rules and standards. The aim of this analysis is to identify in regular intervals, the deviations that may require corrective act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;tax-consulting:a7f4ea7861853ea0de97008ab620749e&#34;&gt;Tax Consulting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer tax consulting services in the level of experts. Our clients are huge companies that need to know more about judicial normative and laws regarding
to economical-financial issues. Our support in this aspect is evident because most of accountants don’t posses the required trainings and adequate experience for
offering this service which continuously must be refreshed  because of dynamics in changes at legal system of Kosovo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;accounting:a7f4ea7861853ea0de97008ab620749e&#34;&gt;Accounting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We offer a full range of book keeping and accounting services for small to mid-sized businesses. Depending on your company’s needs, we partner with you as your bookkeeper, accountant, controller, business advisor, part-time CFO — or the entire department.
By partnering with us to help you manage key non-core functions, you can concentrate efforts on maximizing your core business, which is essential to businesses that are
positioned for growth.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>