<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Golang on TrendBiz</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/golang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Golang on TrendBiz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 04:35:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/golang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 04:35:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/first/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cloud works! Our entire infrastructure is based on Amazon Web Services (AWS). Whether you are a large enterprise, an SME or a startup;
whether you are into banking or education, R&amp;amp;D or service, TrendBiz has the cloud solution befitting your needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We cater to the specific business requirements of each organization. This ensures that all your IT needs are met.
Cloud services facilitate use of the latest, most advanced IT resources without having to buy them. Pay-As-You-Go services can be integrated into your service
plan to help you access better resources at a competent price. Grow faster with better IT resources at your disposal without having to actually own them.
Get higher Computing Power with efficient information transfer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Access your enterprise data and manage it from anywhere around the globe. Pay only for what you use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scale up or scale down your computing capacity within minutes, depending on your needs. Gain quick accessto increased storage and resources.
Choose your specification as per your business. Multiple layers of security to ensure safety and integrity of your data, application and IP.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>